https://elman.com/cookie-policy-us/

Skip to content
Cookie Policy (US)
Home/Cookie Policy (US)
Cookie Policy (US)Gerry Elman2020-04-05T16:53:14-04:00
This page was last changed on April 5, 2020, last checked on April 5, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://elman.com (hereinafter: "the website") uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as "cookies"). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settingsYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Analytical cookiesWe use analytical cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these analytical cookies we get insights in the usage of our website.6.3 Marketing/Tracking cookiesMarketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage, used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.6.4 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesGoogle Analytics
Usage
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Statistics (anonymous)
Name
_ga
Retention
2 years
Function
Name
_gid
Retention
Usage
We use Go Daddy for website hosting.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Go Daddy Privacy Statement.
Purpose pending investigation
Name
_tccl_visitor
Retention
Function
Name
_tccl_visit
Retention
Function
Twitter
Usage
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
metrics_token
Retention
persistent
Function
Stores if the user has seen embedded content
Functional
Usage
We use Complianz for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Complianz Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
cmplz_all
Retention
365 days
Function
Store cookie consent preferences
Name
Usage
We use JetPack for advertising.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the JetPack Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
tk_tc
Retention
session
Function
Store the user's usage history
Functional
Usage
We use LinkedIn for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the LinkedIn Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
X-LI-IDC
Retention
session
Function
Provide functions across pages
WP Do Not Track
Usage
We use WP Do Not Track for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
dont_track_me
Retention
1 year
Function
Store 'do not track' signals
Facebook
Usage
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Marketing/Tracking
Name
actppresence
Retention
1 year
Function
Manage ad display frequency
Name
Usage
We use Vimeo for video display.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Vimeo Privacy Statement.
Statistics
Name
vuid
Retention
2 years
Function
Store the user's usage history
Name
Usage
We use Cookie Notice for GDPR for cookie consent management.
Sharing data
This data is not shared with third parties.
Functional
Name
cookie_notice_accepted
Retention
persistent
Function
Checks if cookies can be placed
Google reCAPTCHA
Usage
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention.
Sharing data
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement.
Functional
Name
rc::c
Retention
session
Function
Filter requests from bots
Name
Function
8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Elman Technology Law, P.C.
12 Veterans Sq., 1st Fl
Media, PA 19063
U.S.A.
United States
Website: https://elman.com
Email: info@elman.com
Phone number: +1 610-892-9942This Cookie Policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on April 5, 2020
Share this:Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)Like this:Like Loading...
Gerry Elman has received a 2019 Martindale-Hubbell® Peer Review Rating of AV Preeminent®
Featured ArticlesRegister for Gerry Elman’s webinar on Non-Disclosure Agreements and Trade Secrets June 16Get Gerry’s slideshow here on The Topsy Turvy World of Fake Products: Catching Trademark CounterfeitersTop 6 Reasons for a Trademark SearchGoogle provides an AI engine to compose harmonies in the style of J.S. BachOur DPAC Presentation on Trade Secrets – December 18, 2018Watch Gene Dolgoff’s video on The Importance of Patents
Recent Articles
Watch Gerry Elman’s January 15, 2020 interview about intellectual property on Money-Matters TV
Register for Gerry Elman’s webinar on Non-Disclosure Agreements and Trade Secrets June 16
Gerry’s chapter on Intellectual Property Protection for Biotechnology Inventions
Are You a HIPAA Business Associate?
June 27, 2019 – Gerry Elman spoke on What Is the Internet of Things (IoT)?
Find us on Facebook
Find us on Facebook
Elman on Tech News via Twitter Tweets by @ElmanTechNews
%d bloggers like this:
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
Go to Top
